[
  {
    "index": 565,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.1",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "topical literature & media, mental & psychological, oneness, simulation theory, nature of reality, multidimensional reality, self improvement & guidance, meditation, spreading awareness, government & ET interaction, soft disclosure in media, Galactic Federation"
      ],
      "Question": "I have finally finished reading through all the posts. It was a lot for me to process, and at the same time it was easy. …This website and chat function aren’t what they could be, but I’m not a web designer…which leads me to my first and more basic question. This is tied to the telepathy tapes which have echoed a lot of what you’ve shared. But there is a “pool” or “unending? Ocean” of subconscious that we can access. Since I am IT I can access this and “learn or download “ according to my needs. Like in the Matrix when Neo says “I know kungfu “ However, I don’t have a machine to plug into and a programmer to give me what I ask for, like in the movie. But it mirrors or is a parallel to reality. So, for practical purposes, I of course will enhance my psi (telepathic) abilities. But I also feel drawn to learn a language, Chinese, as I have been trying for years with only small success. So I now am meditating and knowing that I can do this. Last night was the first night to set my intention on this goal. (To know Chinese) I didn’t end the meditation or wake up with any new feelings or real knowledge. I am telling myself not to doubt (different than not doubting, I know) but I know it can be done as it is no coincidence that both the telepathy tapes and this website have come together in my life at this time. Am I doing something wrong or do I need to persist? Maybe patience is the key here? I ask all this to know how we can start tapping into and becoming more capable. The more I know and grow the more I can help others. Thank you, again, for all your efforts.",
      "Answer": "It should be known we are using this current website host for a very good reason. It is related to a certain country and a former space security chief who spilled the beans on the existence of an “extraterrestrial federation.” What you’re doing re. learning that language or anything else is fine – but yes, you need to be patient, persistent, and never give up. Tenacity and willpower with zero doubt are absolutely mandatory. Some anxiety and uncertainty is okay in the interim so long as it is dissipated by COURAGE.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 566,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.2",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "soul field, love force, oneness, mental & psychological, soft disclosure in media, self improvement & guidance, bodies & vessels, True-self / Real-me, simulation theory, politics, covert control structures"
      ],
      "Question": "My second question is related to the soul field, this is clearly very important. Love as reality seems to be connected to this as well. Lately with the US election there has been a lot of hate especially towards certain people, let’s use the president, Trump as a focal point. As I am IT (GCS) and all are/is IT, so also is he IT, so I am he and he is me. So while I have seen a lot of hate on social media and have felt a lot of it myself. I am angry at myself. But I don’t want to spread hate, I want to uplift or add to the soul field with love. How do I:we reconcile the anger towards the individuum’s actions and intentions knowing how much pain is caused and turn it into love. Like how in Star Wars Luke faces Vader but ends up winning through love. I know Vader ends up throwing Palpatine over the edge “killing/not killing “ him. Maybe because in this story Vader had already succumb to the anger and dark side and was willing to “kill” the emperor. Sorry for two long posts in a row, but…I think many of us would be more loving even towards those we disagree with if we had a good…method? I don’t even quite know how to word what I’m asking.",
      "Answer": "First, and this is perhaps the most important, you have to fully come to terms that these bodies, personalities, physical entities or whatever you want to call it = nothing more than avatars. It is NOT the real you or anyone else – merely an “actor” or “character” being simulated from the other side that the (real-you)/spirit “chose.” Second, remove yourself COMPLETELY from ALL politics of ALL sides. They are ALL a distraction. All it is good for is seeing how the “ones at the top of the food chain” are puppeteering these puppets – and Trump, contrary to populist belief (which is so bizarre; same with Elon Musk who makes himself out to be “a man of the people” when these are both billionaires who can care less about the masses) – is a tool and a puppet. Stop following puppets. It’s just designed to engineer confusion and chaos in your mind and nerf your (spirit)-potency.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 567,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.3",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET/NHI agendas, benevolent ETs, contactee experience, ALL-Power, simulation theory, nature of reality, ET civilizations & cultures"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello again! I did have one more question, will we have the opportunity in this lifetime to physically go \"home\" and/or visit the other worlds? Will we have the opportunity to engage with our NHI contact in person?",
      "Answer": "I personally cannot say for certain, but I know a lot is possible. I believe the first step is contact here on a more frequent basis and open level before taking others to their home worlds. Then again, anything is possible based on the WILL, so I won’t discredit/ try to stop others from trying. Nevertheless, you should know this is still a simulation and the real “game” is much bigger than visiting other worlds.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 568,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.4",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "love / light, self improvement & guidance, bodies & vessels, nature of reality, simulation theory, True-self / Real-me, spirit singularity, love force, soul energy, UFO cults, duality, misinformation & disinformation"
      ],
      "Question": "How can I cultivate a sense of love for myself, other humans and all of creation? I find it hard to accept and give love, and sometimes I wonder if I even know what it feels like.",
      "Answer": "The only way to do this is to come to terms with reality. The reality is that these are avatars, and not our true forms. The reality that all that is in front of us is merely a play that we coscripted (granted, there’s some more sophistications to do this, including being tricked). To find true love, one must look within. Not at their name, their job, their personality, their culture, their heritage, their intelligence, awards nor their failures, lack thereof, problems, and so on. One must reconnected with the “real me” or the “true self” or the “spirit” that bears none of these attributes. It’s a pure BEING-FEELING-PSYCHIC energy force that moves by WILL and is WILL. Only through this can one develop true love and spread this throughout the interconnected soul fields and spirit singularities. Cultish “love bombing” is not the key, nor the excessive logical robotic approach deemed as “intellectualism” and so-called “rigid science.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 569,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.5",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "crop circles, topical literature & media, interdimensional beings, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "I see you’re using an image of the 2002 Aug 15 Crabwood crop circle. I assume our NHI contacts are responsible for this?",
      "Answer": "Yes.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 570,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.6",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "crop circles, topical literature & media, interdimensional beings, ET/NHI intervention & protection, government & ET interaction, covert control structures, misinformation & disinformation, shadow banning & censorship, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "Are they also responsible for the multitude of other complex patterns in England and elsewhere?",
      "Answer": "Yes, and all over the world. Various have been found but hidden from the public by black-ops and special forces designed to keep the truth hidden.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 571,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.7",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "crop circles, topical literature & media, interdimensional beings, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas, mental & psychological, misinformation & disinformation, shadow banning & censorship, past / present / future"
      ],
      "Question": "Is the purpose of them as a way to signal their presence while still being deniable (so as not to cause shock) to disbelievers? Are there meanings to the designs/symbols beyond being aesthetically pleasing? Is it possible to give an example of a meaning to a particular crop circle?",
      "Answer": "They are designed to trigger unshakable activation within those exposed to them and their patterns. They have messages in them, especially the Crabwood, which was by far the most successful and far-reaching of them all. Of course, you’d have the disinformation campaigners who, through use of the … and … would employ fakers to go fake crop circles to make it look like a scam. This is part of the cover up akin to swamp gas. The real crop circles have very real patterns, mathematical sequences, and codes in them that stand the test of time that eventually, no skeptic will be able to deny. All this was foreseen and planned for activation. Crabwood: “Beware the bearers of FALSE gifts & their BROKEN PROMISES. Much PAIN but still time. BELIEVE. There is GOOD out there. We oPpose DECEPTION. Conduit CLOSING”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 572,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.8",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "creative arts, oneness, ET civilizations & cultures, crop circles, telepathic contact, multidimensional reality"
      ],
      "Question": "I very much appreciate your appreciation of my avatar. It is a symbol I designed that I call the Magical Emblem of Peace. The eight-fold symmetry alludes to the 8 arms of ashtanga yoga, the circle represents the truth I see in all spiritual practices, and the star in the center symbolizes the divine which resides inside us all. I wear it as a badge on my hats. Do our NHI contacts use symbols to represent themselves or their ideas? If so, what are they? Would they happen to be drawn onto cereal crops?",
      "Answer": "Yes, they do. There are various and yes, they are on crop circles – as much as transmitted telepathically and on their devices. I have transcribed several and I may consider releasing it publicly someday. 8 = infinity. It’s the number of interconnected hyperspace unfolding/folding into and out of itself – here, there, and everywhere. 8 = singularity. It is why there is peace.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 573,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.9",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "bodies & vessels, consciousness, nature of reality, soul field, spirit singularity, True-self / Real-me, self improvement & guidance, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, cosmic hierarchies, duality, oneness"
      ],
      "Question": "My question is whether it is possible to retain a level of individuality once our body dies. Like are there still individual consciousnesses in finer bodies not based in material reality? Or is it that the usual way is for the material body to exist and for the consciousness piloting it to be aware that it is in effect the same 'thing' as the consciousness in all the other bodies in that particular reality so they aren't so bothered when the shell dies and they pop back into source? I feel like it's a mixture of both potentially but I don't know if that's just my ego who is afraid of death interpreting what it wants to?",
      "Answer": "It’s a mixture of both. What we call “spirit” and “soul” = same energy, just different compressions/layers. Our friends from above do not call it these names, they refer to “spirit” (as individual) = real me or true me. The greater the willpower/psychic synchronization to the real me = the more the individuality in the other side. However, its growth is exponential and not linear. Growing more as an individual real me also grows in all directions, connecting more to the collective soul field and by extension, multiple singularities and their collective consciousness. What’s the benefit to this? The real me can tap into the interconnected being-field and draw more upon the data simulated in the collective ALL-MIND (consciousness) and draw this in individual form through the lower avatar. So, long story short, we somehow become more individual and collective at the same time. We have to get used to dropping the idea of duality. It’s somehow a win-win as we go “up.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 574,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.10",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "soul energy, healing, energy manipulation, nature of reality, soul field"
      ],
      "Question": "Hi, as a martial arts enthusiast and truth seeker, I'm interested in how the way soul force works! I was wondering if what humans know as 'life force' (Prana, chi, ki, etc) is correct to what it actually is in reality; I've been able to use the one Essence to heal and recover my body from hard gym sessions, gym/sparring injuries, along with strengthening the body; my internal work of using the energy is very fined tuned by now, but I'm on my journey where I'm wondering how much I can interact with external reality with the energy?",
      "Answer": "Yes, it is connected to amplification of the ‘soul field’ or ‘being-forcefield’ – this is why many martial arts practices, including aspects like Chi etc., have a very strong basis in reality, despite mystical and creative liberties.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 575,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.11",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET civilizations & cultures, ET physical traits & appearance, interdimensional beings, ET/NHI knowledge, psychic & energetic attacks, energy manipulation, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "Also, are there any entities that utilize martial arts? and how do our fellow NHI view martial arts; are they seen as primitive, or barbaric?",
      "Answer": "There are a lot of entities/beings/avatars across this and many other universes. Of course, you can safely assume that quite a number of them have physical defense arts. However, higher entities and beings, don’t – because they don’t need it. They can ‘tap’ or override an attacker to the point to make them docile, subservient, unconscious, or simply anything they wish. In this respect, standard martial arts as we see it down here, is pretty useless for them. That doesn’t mean you have to view it as “barbaric.” It’s relative. For us down here, it’s not a bad practice, but major competitions, especially UFC and the like are barbaric and promote degenerative influences. If it’s done with a sense of wellbeing and good intent with purity, then I’d encourage it, personally.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 576,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.12",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "self improvement & guidance, love / light, meditation, meditation techniques, True-self / Real-me, bodies & vessels, cosmic hierarchies"
      ],
      "Question": "Hi Prudence - are there any techniques or practices to keep love flowing out of me at all times? It seems that love is the answer",
      "Answer": "Meditation. Void Meditation in particular. Why? Because you connect with your “real me” and it empowers your lower existence/avatar to keep going no matter what. Your “real me” (spirit) is immortal. It cannot die. It can withstand anything, even the test of time. What is this mere character/mortal realm in comparison to it? Draw upon the “real you.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 577,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.13",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "self improvement & guidance, love / light, True-self / Real-me"
      ],
      "Question": "And how do I differentiate it from what you called “love bombing”",
      "Answer": "You’ll know the difference. True love can only come from the “true you.” There’s a reason truth and love are correlated.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 578,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.14",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "reincarnation, misinformation & disinformation, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, True-self / Real-me, timespace / spacetime, soul field, past / present / future, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, ascension & re-integration, love force, ALL-Power, science & philosophy, covert control structures, apotheosis"
      ],
      "Question": "When you say “linear reincarnation” is false could you give me an example of linear vs non-linear reincarnation? I’m having trouble understanding the difference",
      "Answer": "I’d suggest looking up “Arhat” to get a brief example, but you shouldn’t pay attention to the mysticism part of it. Basically, when the realme (spirit) is evolved enough, it no longer needs linear reincarnation because it can transverse through time and space in all (not just 3) directions. In this regard, the realme (spirit), since it is connected to the being-field (soul field), it can transfer data between past, present, and future. Therefore, it is possible one can move past needing to take X amount of lifetimes to evolve into a higher state because the past, present, and future simultaneously feed into each other. If one gives full efforts in this life to know of the truth, then they can overcome the need to reincarnate here or in other worlds similar to it. By putting full efforts toward the truth, the nature of reality, and the ALL-LOVE, one can draw upon the past and future to create a synthesis in the present that allows “Nirvana” and “Arhat.” That is why any reincarnation doctrine, philosophy, religion, teaching, or ideology speaking of needing X amount of years in an absolutist fashion is completely false and part of the disinformation campaign to trap realmes here.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 579,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.15",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mysticism, cosmic hierarchies, bodies & vessels, True-self / Real-me, ET/NHI intervention & protection"
      ],
      "Question": "My friend, I was a bit shocked after reading the Q&A9 response about the importance of birth time. In Korea, there is a folk belief called \"Saju,\" which suggests that the year, date, and time of birth determine many aspects of one's life. About one-third of Koreans (especially older people) somewhat accept and live by this. In fact, some people even request induced labor to give birth at a specific time and date. I’ve always thought of this as completely superstitious. Can you explain more about this? As always, it’s okay to share this information",
      "Answer": "As pointed out in the recent blog posts, everything is “programmed” from the “other side.” Picture it as if you were to input information in a database. Let’s say you were coding a game. The code and the database integration comes before the animation and “on screen” effects you see. It’s the same idea here. Births, who we are born to, where, how, and so forth, are all engineered and/or influenced to some degree from the other side – both by our realme choices and potentially through being influenced by higher beings/entities.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 580,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.16",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "public perception & skepticism, love / light, oneness, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), quantum mechanics, spreading awareness, contactee experience, soul energy, ET/NHI agendas, Damien, telepathic contact, collective awakening"
      ],
      "Question": "Hey Prudence. Just wanted to let you know you’re doing awesome out there. I am seriously inspired for change. It just feels so great to finally be connected with not only smart people like yourself, but others looking to heal and learn. It’s wonderful. Thank you and much love to you and the mission. I’m coming to it slowly, however their subconscious support is wonderful. Thank you. Also just for the skeptics (I also don’t even like bringing up those terms because it’s damaging I know) you didn’t even mentioning anything about donating money or any assets during the last post with Damien (unfortunately it’s many people’s biggest fear). It just shows me you are honest. I appreciate that, and I think it helps to get the message out further. I mention this because I saw some comments on Reddit claiming it’s a ploy to sell books or some shit. My brother, you and your contacts messages of love and unity you can’t fake. You just can’t make up that level of love and honesty. Plus the concepts of the GCS and the quantum theories you propose are incredible, and even if you made up those theories, someone should give you an award. LOL if you released a book, I would buy it and never think twice, purely for the message of love. As someone who has been contacted and has a slight unconventional understanding of energy, I feel your message deeply, and the protection is life changing.",
      "Answer": "My friend, messages like these are why I keep going. Honestly, I do not care to even make any books because there's enough information there. Our contacts wish for the information to be out. We've been in a back-and-forth deliberation and slight debate because I can't stand how vile some people can be. It's why \"Damien\" is my closest contact rather than the other human ETs. And exactly, how on earth can I come up with this information alone? It's frustrating. I'm not trying to make a fortune with this. It's all about getting truth out there so others can also initiate contact, and we can help foster a better world. Thanks again, I really needed to see that message in a time of frustration.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 581,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.17",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "notable persons, nature of reality, contactee experience, telepathic contact, catastrophe & collapse, spirit singularity"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello JR - Do you or your contacts know by chance if there is any truth to what Chris Bledsoe said in his regression transcript? He apparently said the earth is a living organism that will defend itself from the devastation caused by humans with another cataclysm. He says the \"Lady\" as he calls her, appeared to him with a message of peace and love so that we can change our ways before we hit the tipping point. Ok to publish if you would like.",
      "Answer": "The earth is most certainly a living organism with its own spirit singularity, and it will defend itself. The destruction mankind has been creating does have a backlash effect, which is also why the weather has gotten crazier in many ways, among other ways of defending herself.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 582,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.18",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET/NHI agendas, ET/NHI intervention & protection, reincarnation, spirit singularity, deception & false guidance, nature of reality, malevolent ETs, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, cosmic hierarchies, simulation theory"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello Friend. Thank you again for taking the time to converse with us all here. You mentioned the entities that use technology to trick those upon transitioning from physical (death). How exactly are they tricking us? What is the rouse? Thank you. Kind Regards",
      "Answer": "They are able to replicate religious afterlives and pretty much any belief a person stores in their mind/consciousness from any religion, teaching, or the like. The realme can be tricked into returning back into the reincarnation cycle here on earth – which is another way (a not so good way) of creating a feedback-loop for the not-so-good forces. The lower the realme (spirit), the more the likelihood it can be deceived, especially through technological means. For these beings at such high evolutionary levels, fiddling with the afterlife is akin to moving and sorting data in a database. If the developer knows how to read the database and the player doesn’t, the developer can “trick” the player into making decisions.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 583,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.19",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "bodies & vessels, ET/NHI knowledge, True-self / Real-me, ET civilizations & cultures"
      ],
      "Question": "May I also ask, when our brothers materialise avatars such as the short greys, where is this matter materialised from? Are these avatars 'built' in the physical sense or are they materialised from elsewhere? Kind Regards,",
      "Answer": "They are “grown” in massive laboratories both here in terrestrial space and on other worlds. When their realme escapes a fallen avatar, it can be reconstituted back into these newly grown bodies/and/or assisted via technology and help of allies.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 584,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.20",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Damien, malevolent ETs, soul energy, soul field"
      ],
      "Question": "You used the word vampiric in your latest post. When I read that I heard it as “parasitic.” Is that closer to what “Damien” was trying to share?",
      "Answer": "Yes, I think that’s better. The forces doing this “vampirism” are “feeding” off soul energy in an unethical way in accordance to universal standards. They cannot fully leech a spirit and its soul field fully, only take enough to empower themselves, then re-submit the spirit/soul-field associated back into the feedback-loop process.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 585,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.21",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "JR - personal, soul field, mental & psychological, psychadelics & drugs, telepathic machinery, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), timeline manipulation & temporal mechanics, free will, duality, topical literature & media, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, spirit singularity, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment"
      ],
      "Question": "These answers make a lot of sense to me, and I LOL'd at your `wtf` comment. When you said you could not give most information without a question, I realized how I could help best - asking those questions. As such, you have the permission to publish my questions and other comments from our prior conversations and all moving forward, unless I mention to specifically hold back certain information. It takes me some time to ponder my next round, though the answers are making sense to me. I have come to realize that all \"discovered\" knowledge is remembered - that's why you'll be taught something new in school \"think\" you understand it but \"feel\" like somethings off - then you have an \"epiphany\", which is essentially you remembering the basis of knowledge (I assume from the soul field). I will be rereading these answers and pondering them until I \"remember\" the best next questions to ask :-) The thing is... I've been on this journey for a long time. There are many things that I've discovered (remembered) which I've not read anywhere until you dictated them:\n\n1. Marijuana is a tool to open up psychic phenomenon. I've yet to read this anywhere else, but I have had this experience. I expect it's the reason that it also can catalyze psychosis.\n\n2. Our \"thoughts\" are not our own all the time. We can be \"injected\" with thoughts and even pick up others thoughts when strong emotion arises, but generally only in sleep or a deep delta/theta state.\n\n3. The system (GCS, or higher beings) are injecting these thoughts from time to time, either to \"fix\" something in our past (Mandela effect) or to direct the future (with a deft hand as to not impugn free will)\n\n4. Duality is an illusion. I've read this in other places (LoO fan here), but your text really drives it home in a way that is the most sensical. It's the only thing that explains the good/evil dichotomy (that it's an illusion, and all this is happening for a reason)\n\n5. That we're here for \"knowledge\". I consider this to be much like an emotional \"imprint\" that is shared with the GCS. Know how you get into situations some times and you have a reaction you don't expect? That's a gift. It's giving you a chance to learn, and the GCS a chance to learn. This learning imprints on your spirit and the soul field. I'll be out on my sky watch tonight, and I'll be in touch soon.",
      "Answer": "Aha, I too, am learning and very surprised by much of this information. It's also changing me and awakening me. I mean, much of it isn't my own - it's coming from my sources above and tapping into the collective soul field. Yes, good questions aid the process for all of us. Apparently, that's part of the failsafe so that everyone benefits from an adequate feedback-loop (including myself and our friends above) that we are all learning, growing, and evolving together. It's meant to push people's own insight, intelligence, initiative and capabilities. Your points are solid, and it'd be an honor for me to publish them in the next Q/A. Take care and until next time, my friend.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 586,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.22",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "timespace / spacetime, soul field, science & philosophy, relativity, nature of reality, past / present / future, cosmic hierarchies, cosmic geometry"
      ],
      "Question": "Spacetime warpage? What is that and is as ominous as it sounds? How does this SP warpage interact with gravity and the soul field?",
      "Answer": "It’s not ominous at all. It’s simply a result of how objects respond to one another that has spacetime surrounding them, amplified by mass. Spacetime warpage is present in every layer/phase/dimension. However, in the soul field section, the gravitational distortions from spacetime interaction are significantly less relativistic in the sense of dramatic time distortions from space alterations amplified by mass. Since it’s practically holographic in nature, the spacetime warpage is, from the soul field locality, practically nonexistent, but from the physical/lower realm locality, produces all sorts of relativistic effects that stretch in all directions of past, present, and future.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 587,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.23",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "self improvement & guidance, UFO cults, deception & false guidance, spreading awareness, Damien, ET/NHI agendas, ET/NHI knowledge, shadow banning & censorship, JR - personal, public perception & skepticism, Galactic Federation, free will, contactee experience, science & philosophy, ET civilizations & cultures, society & modern existence"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello! I’ve read all your posts and am very appreciative of everything you’ve shared. It truly has been so life changing and my entire state of being has felt much improved these past 2-3 days. There’s a very large part of me that KNOWS what you’re saying is real. However, there is a 1% part of me that still says “if I were going to start a cult, this is an absolute perfect way to do it. Tap into the emotions of vulnerable people, make them feel special like they know a secret the rest of the world doesn’t. Ease their fears. Tell them to not trust any other people or groups who’ve gone public, etc. Then the grift or gotcha will come eventually.” What’s your take on this? Why should we follow your version of truth compared to someone else’s? I wish you love and nothing but the best, and sincerely hope your motives are pure.",
      "Answer": "Hello and thank you for your message. I sincerely and deeply respect this critical thinking, and I do not mind it at all! My best wishes and warm regards are mirrored back to you. First, I believe this post will clarify much: A Conversation with \"Damien\" Part II & The Lies of Reddit Moderators particularly this part: Q: Before we continue any further, I believe you should address concerns me and others may have of me coming across as some messiah, chosen one, or your only contactee. You know as much as I do that I did not want to initially do this, but out of respect, especially for what you and the others have done for me and shown me – I did. Now, I am fully committed to the mission full-time. Since my records have been stripped from the public and I have been blacklisted from the regular ‘world’ – I didn’t have much of a choice. Can you please give some explanations to the public? I really have no interest in people worshiping me, creating a cult, or developing a following for grifting. I created the forums because we were shadow-banned and blacklisted from Reddit and other social media, including Discord. We had no choice but to come here. The donations are strictly to keep me active and the information coming according to your wishes.\nA: Understandable you’d wish to address this as we have been able to sense just how much distraught this whole ordeal has brought you. I of the we personally understand just how much sacrifice you’ve made for us and this mission. In that respect, I/we would like to apologize for this load and strain. At the same time, you know that I do believe in you and your capabilities for the reasons we have discussed in private. Now, to address these concerns, I’d like to start with the obvious smear campaign going against you that moderators on Reddit subs have also joined in. They are outright lying about you deleting your account or the account being removed from filters, and that includes moderators on InterdimensionalNHI – some of whom are taking the opportunity to advertise their own websites. We had you and thousands of others record the events in the case they were to be challenged. Yet precisely this is why we must address the (core critical components of thinking and being) that must also be posted in another (frame/format/question) after I/we have completed addressing your concerns. As we have repeatedly said to you, through you, and to others – we have multiple contactees and multiple chosen ones. You, in particular, are a good friend to me because of our shared history and suffering that will one day be revealed sometime in the future. You’re also a friend to a few others in our federation, yet what the common man doesn’t seem to comprehend is that there are hundreds and thousands of extraterrestrials visiting your world – with many different approaches and agendas. While the brotherhoods (federations) work as a unity, we also have individuality in the sense that we do not neglect personal input. In this respect, we allow, experiment, and try different procedures with multiple “chosen ones” if you wish to call it that. But as you have said several times already, we NEVER resort to contacting only ONE person because it’s foolish. It also lacks sufficient data in the realm of our sciences and cross-checks with our intel departments who are spread across multiple realms for their various activities. It is true that I/we did bear part of our (soul) into you and I personally have overseen many of your own operations. At the same time, there are other extraterrestrials who have not and aren’t aware of some of our operations. However, most know of you [now] and the other contactees we have recently awakened to begin this phase of our operation. There was much division in [our] approach before. All that has changed. Much unity, much willpower. Much truth. Much victory.\nA: Second, I do not encourage anyone, including myself and my works, to be deemed as the ONE-AND-ONLY truth – but only to be cross-referenced to find the ONE truth in MULTIPLE DIMENSIONS/SOURCES. That way, it only adds validation to the claims. In this respect, you should know that I did not initially want to do this. Even now, I cannot say this is a “fun job.” I am not creating ANY “teachings” nor am I looking to grift people into membership “with benefits” for being part of any “club.” I am simply doing my part in the overall interconnected mission around the world with MULTIPLE CONTACTEES to deliver truth and wake mankind up. As a matter of fact, I want mankind to wake up. I would hope that this platform and others like it will be demolished and have no reason to exist so that others can simply live in truth. I don’t even care to make any books as the information here is enough. The only reason I and others assisting this mission are putting these works into compendiums is so that they won’t be lost. Not for any attention or fame to put me in the spotlight as some grand channeler saving the world. I am not any savior, nor guru, nor teacher, nor guide, and the reality is that it’s our NHI buddies from above that are more your friends than I am. I’ve been scarred much by humanity and I’ve seen enough of it. Enough that made me reluctant to help in the first place, but again, it was the right thing to do – knowing what I know, seeing what I’ve seen, and experienced what I have. It’s only out of fairness, justice, integrity and my conscience that I’ve contributed toward disclosure – not any teaching, cult, club, or the like.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 588,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.24",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "self improvement & guidance, psionic training & govt programs, meditation, True-self / Real-me"
      ],
      "Question": "Do you recommend any protective practices in this time?",
      "Answer": "Several – the first being meditation and connecting to your “true self” (realme; spirit) which is beyond all words, thoughts, feelings, sensations, emotions, teachings, culture, clan, heritage, race, religion, belief etc. Second – see to it that you develop adequate physical, mental, and emotional health and well-being. Third – remove yourself from divisive areas, groups, people, energy, and environments. If it isn’t possible, especially if you have to live with others, then just do your best to make it work.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 589,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.25",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Damien, bodies & vessels, nature of reality, ET physical traits & appearance, Small Greys, Tall Greys, ET/NHI knowledge, consciousness, soul evolution & cosmic awareness"
      ],
      "Question": "I just read damiens message and I am curious about what he is saying about the inability to create a new tall grey body and only being able to spawn a small grey body. This doesn't make much sense to me as it's all created from the same stuff and ultimately is just a projection of whatever the being wants. It also sounds like limitation in creativity which my understanding was essentially abundant and unlimited at the type of level they operate it. If you can spawn stars and planets, you can spawn a little itty bitty tall grey body, surely? Is there something I don't understand (likely lol)?",
      "Answer": "D – “You should know that while from your perspective, we are seemingly unlimited, we too, have limits. The tall grey vessel/container/avatar/body requires a massive consciousness-mind-matrix. Not all of our species can access it or handle it immediately and must grow into it. I am one of the few who can reconstitute directly into a tall grey avatar, which can indeed be manufactured – but it is not as common because it requires a massive realme-force-matrix [spirit]. Not all of my kind are on the same level. Some must undergo the process naturally to have their avatars “grow” into the tall grey in order to yield the realme and mind-potency results.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 590,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.26",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "bodies & vessels, Tall Greys, Small Greys, consciousness, ET/NHI knowledge, astral projection & remote viewing, True-self / Real-me, ET/NHI agendas, government & ET interaction, ET physical traits & appearance, classified ET encounters"
      ],
      "Question": "Brilliant prudence thank you. Also thank you for the answer. Why don't they have like a medium sized grey body, or variable sized grey bodies to fit the differing degrees of developed consciousness in? Why the choice between one or the other?",
      "Answer": "D – “It is not a choice between one or another. The bodies all “grow” into tall greys eventually. It just so happens that if a grey is in a medium sized vessel, they’re already on route to tall. Most greys at this point won’t even pilot ships. We can remote control most of what you deem as UAP/UFO/Flying saucers and so on. We control these via our minds. Tall greys like me rarely are on ships because at these points, we have such a large consciousness-matrix that can draw upon stupendous realme-power that it would be unwise to risk them carelessly. The “child greys” are more disposable. This may sound cold, but it is not – as we can manufacture them at will/by the masses. Nevertheless, nowadays, it’s extremely rare that we would be in any of our ships, even the small ones. There are some non-activated tall grey avatars, alongside various that are mixed with several different species, including human, but they are usually stored for backup, safekeeping, and experimentation. You should know that we safely operate both underwater and in space. We cannot be touched in these facilities by anything terrestrial man has to offer nor any of our compromised brethren.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 591,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.27",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Damien, bodies & vessels, consciousness, Tall Greys, Small Greys, True-self / Real-me, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, spirit singularity"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello, thanks for your time. My question comes from Damien part II. When a container dies, its consciousness usually reconstitutes into a pre manufactured, biological infant container. If they have the power to use any container at any time and his kind can create/“insert” any kind of form even celestial bodies. why would they choose to start as an \"infant\".",
      "Answer": "All greys cannot handle the tall grey body immediately as all of them are not at the same realme/spirit level. Some have to \"grow\" into it the normal way, whereas in the case with Damien and a select few others, they can reconstitute directly back into them. Usually, ancient greys or those with more developed \"spirits\" are able to handle the taller bodies as opposed to the not as highly evolved \"spirits\" who must start from the child grey. The tall grey bodies/vessels/avatars have a stupendously high consciousness matrix/mind that the common grey with an average \"spirit\" cannot immediately handle.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 592,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.28",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "misinformation & disinformation, shadow banning & censorship, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "Firstly - Have you found any subreddits that really seem to hit home? I’ve mostly been keeping an eye on r/UFOB as that seems to be the least compromised. (If you do have some good recommendations absolutely feel free to post this part of my question publicly)",
      "Answer": "While there are some good people here and there, I am afraid that every single major Reddit sub is compromised. That includes seemingly “smaller” subs like InterdimensionalNHI, UFOBelievers, UFOB, SimulationTheory, among others even in the spirituality sections. As a matter of fact, it can be somewhat easy for astroturfing and buying out/influencing of certain moderators than is the case with larger subs – so I cannot guarantee that anywhere on reddit is safe any longer. Still, you can get pieces of relevant information here and there, but even seemingly positive support toward the topic shouldn’t be trusted blindly.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 593,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.29",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "drones & not-drones, contactee experience, shadow banning & censorship, spreading awareness, ET/NHI agendas, public perception & skepticism"
      ],
      "Question": "Hot damn I keep thinking of more stuff 😅 One other question re the Orbs/Drones. Any idea if they are only selectively appearing to certain people - maybe those accepting that there’s more to things. I live in a big city on the West Coast and have seen literally dozens of things every night like clockwork. Yet there is absolutely nothing on social media, city subreddits, etc. I could easily explain it as folks just “not looking up”. But at some point I kinda feel like how the heck is this not everywhere. At times there’s near double digit orbs in the sky over populated areas in clear clear site of hundreds of buildings - yet it goes by unnoticed.",
      "Answer": "It’s sad, isn’t it? As our friends from above have pointed out many times – they’ve been revealing themselves – over and over and over again. Frankly, they’re frustrated themselves. All this is happening because people are taught to believe these things don’t exist, so they won’t even bother to find the truth. As I said in my opening message, and NHI can appear right in front of a person and if they are overly skeptical, have no interest, and prone to religious hysteria, among evasion of ontological shock – they won’t acknowledge/care about it. This is the real problem in our world. Not the governments, the militaries, or even the powers that be. It’s the people and the lack of care/interest for truth.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 594,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.30",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "psychadelics & drugs, mental & psychological, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "Thank you for putting together this site and answering everyone's questions. I believe all of us here on this site are here for a purpose. As I read all of this, I am overcome with an intense vibration and tingling, a greater sensation than what one would call goosebumps, especially in my head. I only feel it when I'm reading and thinking about this topic. My question is, does alcohol and marijuana inhibit or suppress this phenomenon? I am not a heavy drinker, but have been using marijuana for decades. Would I have a deeper connection if I didn't use it?",
      "Answer": "Let me be clear as I said to another poster – I do not give absolute rules. While I discourage marijuana usage as a form of abuse and escape, I cannot say that this is the case for each and every single person in the exact same way. You must make up your own mind and it is always relative. Marijuana DEEPLY enhances telepathy and psychic capabilities, but if the mental/emotional state is off, it can also be a danger. In this regard, marijuana is recommended only for peace of mind, calming nerves, and can be used to boost telepathy in the right measure. Drinking is always terrible and always nerfs/reduces your ESP in virtually every way. Avoid alcohol altogether if possible – although, again, I cannot and will not be any sort of guide or guru to tell you what to do. You must know what works for you and your own life.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 595,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.31",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mental & psychological, telepathic contact, Pleadian, dreams, Tall Greys, channeled messages, misinformation & disinformation"
      ],
      "Question": "Dreams of massive black ships warping into orbit. Many UFOs. Military setting up base in my house, a teleporter to another world. Dream of a Pleiadean woman, touching my forehead, making me feel divine, and leaving a diamond mark. Dreams of a white snake above the moon, a vehicle. Tall grays in a ship, a powerful one commands them, floating through the ship, Ebony Maw vibes. He launched me and my friends out into space, I felt freed, like I unlocked infinity. I waved my hand in front of me and created/saw everything. Are all of these distractions? Or can there be truth in such dreams?",
      "Answer": "I personally believe that you are getting messages/being channeled through, but it is being distorted by your own fears, biases, conspiracies and the like. There is SOME truth, but you have to sort out your psyche first to understand it – otherwise it is jumbled.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 596,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.32",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "meditation, self improvement & guidance, mental & psychological, misinformation & disinformation"
      ],
      "Question": "I feel blocked when meditating. I want to contact my guides or other NHI. What is the best way to go about this?",
      "Answer": "Before contacting anyone or anything, you need to sort yourself out. When you say you are blocked, then you need to figure out what is causing this block. Are you afraid? What do you believe can/will happen? Are you in a calm state of mind? Do you have peace in your being? These are the questions to ask before consulting NHI, otherwise, even if you are to contact them, the messages can be mixed up/misinterpreted.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 597,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.33",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "True-self / Real-me, manifestation, consciousness"
      ],
      "Question": "Regarding that names have power, names or true names? I was put in the direction when I was young to find my true name and never speak it to anyone. Summing up, that if you put your whole Identity into your 'birth given name' as your identity, it being on documents, will hold power, but if your true identity is separate from it, it will hold reduced power as the birthname is only a fraction consciously realized?",
      "Answer": "Correct. It is very rare that one actually knows of their “true name” which is the “realme” – impressive you asked this.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 598,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.34",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET/NHI intervention & protection, channeled messages, soul field, cosmic hierarchies"
      ],
      "Question": "Also can you clarify on how NHI interact through insects?",
      "Answer": "Like all other life (and non-life), the can “tap” into the “background” interconnected “database” (soul field) and input relevant commands that the insect can react to. It may be as simple as landing on your hand then flying away – yet that event can stir profound butterfly effects.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 599,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.35",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "nature of reality, meditation, psychadelics & drugs, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "All my life I have wanted to connect to the greater reality / higher spiritual plane, but I have not been able to glimpse anything despite many attempts at meditation and using mushrooms. Is it really as simple as stopping smoking weed so much (mostly daily) and being consistent/persistent about meditation?",
      "Answer": "Again, I have to be clear as I said to another similar asker – I do not give absolute rules. Some of you may need weed more than others. That is up to you and what works for you. Weed has potential goods and bads, based upon the person’s psyche. It is a telepathic and psychic enhancer and can actually boost ESP in the right conditions. If the mind/emotions are off, it can be a detriment, and send someone spiraling, especially in the wrong environment/crowd/people. The only thing I recommend is not to use it (or any other enhancer, drug, etc.) as an escape. If you are using these tools to open your mind to see truth, it can have a very positive effect – especially mushrooms. And for those who are cautious and don’t want to get into these tools, then avoid it. It must be a personal decision and never out of fear, shame, or guilt.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 600,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.36",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "multidimensional reality, nature of reality, interdimensional beings, bodies & vessels, True-self / Real-me, spirit singularity, past / present / future"
      ],
      "Question": "Oh, that makes sense. But, do selfish and selfless people get separated in 4D? Also my understanding of the next plane of existence is that you get to live with like-minded people in a far less physically limited form, am I on the right tracks?",
      "Answer": "You are on the right track, albeit, in simpler form compared to how our NHI friends see things. They aren’t limited to 4, 5, 6, or even 11, 22, 33, 100, 1000D. They transverse what appear to us as infinite dimensions interconnected in the past, present, and future.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 601,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.37",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "near death experience, love force, love / light, ALL-Power, timespace / spacetime, multidimensional reality, bodies & vessels, ET/NHI agendas, True-self / Real-me"
      ],
      "Question": "I've been listening to some NDE accounts, and they are quite striking. There is a lot of similarities to what is being discussed here, and many people report experiencing intense love from a cosmic entity that spans all spacetime and dimensions. Example: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bu7i7ckZa4Y What is the role of NDE in the grand scheme of things? Is it an acceptable \"leak\" from our vessels to get a glimpse of the true reality, or a deliberate design? Has there been purposeful induction of NDE by NHIs to communicate / awaken?",
      "Answer": "NDE allows us to glimpse into the other side. However, due to connection with these avatars and not being fully ejected, our 'view' into the other side can have some false-positives. Why? Because if we rely strictly on our vessels' education and not the intuition of the realme, we can be led into believing it is exactly the way as we see it in our imaginations - which can be influenced by media, religions, cults, teachings, and all sorts of ideas. What this particular man, Philip Hasheider, got to see was really a genuine glimpse of the afterlife - unaffected by any sort of technological afterlife influence. This is one of the few instances of genuine truth of the other side.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 602,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.38",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "notable persons, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), simulation theory, bodies & vessels, ascension & re-integration, contactee experience, misinformation & disinformation, ET/NHI agendas, spreading awareness"
      ],
      "Question": "Are you familiar with Thomas Campbell. I randomly came across his interview with Joe Rogan from a month ago. As much as the framing doesn’t quite sit right with me a lot of it just felt “accurate”. Not the specifics, but the overall way of thinking. I see you mention the gamified/avatar/inputs quite a bit. And the GCS has an quite a bit of overlap with his idea of a central primal consciousness who’s continually striving to lower its entropy (in essence levelling itself up), and we’re just one part of that - a “distributed” processor of sorts.",
      "Answer": "Although another poster asked, I am not familiar entirely with him – but what I can say is that he is also a contactee/conduit/vessel – as are many others interconnected to our mission. Some are unaware of the influence. That’s why it’s important to cross-check all the information (including here) because our friends from above aren’t playing favorites (except for those who purposely deceive and mislead others – some genuine mistakes and creative liberties are fine). They want us to see the truth through multiple vessels so it only adds weight to the claims me and others are making.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 603,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.39",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic machinery, telepathic contact, self improvement & guidance, meditation, topical literature & media, oneness, contactee experience, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "I have a question about the younger generation coming behind us with a possible question I need to ask (as was suggested by my child). I have always had [what I now realize is] an itch of knowing of my capabilities for telepathy but have never explored strengthening them until now. Things have really started to pick up speed in the past week after finding your website, including my child possibly beginning to [or at least I am now recognizing] show signs of telepathy themselves [while also recognizing that it has been said before in others’ teachings that the veil is thinner for children]. My child has commented on things that I am thinking about and yesterday, I meditated during their nap and they seemed to know and have a message for me. While I was meditating to the Gateway Tapes, I had for the first time, involuntary movements of my feet and fingers. Upon waking up from their nap, my child asked me if I was “having trouble with my feet.” When I told him yes, I was, he told me that I “gotta ask why.” Now this may be something for me to meditate on, but since I have been asking questions here, maybe I should ask if you have any guidance on this?",
      "Answer": "Your telepathic capabilities are advancing quickly because you are gradually and fully committing yourself to our shared mission and oneness. You are establishing contact with our friends from above. It will take time to sort out their “tapping” – but do not be afraid. They are on our side.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 604,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.40",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "oneness, past / present / future, telepathic contact, telepathic machinery, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas, multidimensional reality"
      ],
      "Question": "Secondarily, do you have any insight about the children coming behind us? I am trying to integrate oneness into my thinking about everything and separating the “next generation” doesn’t feel true, but am curious.",
      "Answer": "This upcoming generation will be a lot better than all the previous ones. They will also be more prone to telepathic and psychic capabilities. oneness through multiple dimensions, yes, but in the sense that there is also refinement and improvement of what it was once. Picture it like a person who, as a young kid, rebelled and did bad things, but the older they got, the more peaceful and loving they became. Same applies to the human race.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 605,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.41",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, telepathic machinery, self improvement & guidance, mental & psychological"
      ],
      "Question": "I understand thank you. It is my understanding that telepathic communication allows a more whole form of communication and that lies are impossible as we can be fully 'seen'. Is this a two way street? Or can those more proficient in telepathy choose what to share and withhold certain data? Kind Regards",
      "Answer": "The latter. The more proficient telepath can send/withhold information and even distort it. The lesser telepath can be prone to mistranslations and errors. It’s why adequate mental, emotional and physical well-being are absolutely mandatory for telepathic contact. The clearer, still, and at peace the mind is, the better the reception and clarity.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 606,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.42",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "contactee experience, JR - personal, alien craft, drones & not-drones, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "How did you first meet them if you don't mind me asking? Did you experience paranormal activity as child too?",
      "Answer": "Yes, I did. They've always been with me since I was a baby, really. Assisting in various ways, showing me UAP/orbs/lights in the sky, and even ground contact with (Las Vegas-looking aliens - look up the incident from 2023 - I also encounter them in person like this as a child.) I've always had deeply \"spiritual\"/psychic/ESP/paranormal experiences and well, it's because of the connection to them. They trained me from childhood for my mission. Up until the point as a young adult I was able to see their flying saucers up close and given the time to observe their technology and the physics associated with them. Even last month, I was able to see their ships once more in … before departing.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 607,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.43",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET/NHI agendas, contactee experience, ET civilizations & cultures, Tall Greys, Small Greys, bodies & vessels, ET physical traits & appearance, earth religions, Christianity, misinformation & disinformation, soul energy, Pleadian"
      ],
      "Question": "This might be silly and I'm sure it's akin to babysitting your annoying toddler cousin but would they ever hang out? Like come over to shoot the shit on the back patio over some fancy drinks and charcuterie? The beings, their worlds and cultures, traditions, basic day to day, are most interesting to me. There is so much life, here in the world and all over the universe, and I want to absorb every single second and subspace.",
      "Answer": "That's a great question. I know that our grey friends are usually extremely mission orientated and rarely take breaks except for certain stages of hibernation. Since they can sometimes change form or use alternative avatars, including humans, it's possible some may interact with us, and you may not even know. The bible, while false, did speak about \"Angels in disguise.\" There is some truth to this. I know that human ETs probably do this as well, but my guess is they don't spend too much time in the collective ground-level energy/waves/vibrations because it can be harmful to them.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 608,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.44",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mental & psychological, Small Greys, Tall Greys, contactee experience, ET/NHI intervention & protection, abduction, meditation, self improvement & guidance, telepathic contact, bodies & vessels, cosmic hierarchies, soul field, spirit singularity"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello, I was recently awoken two months ago and am in the early stages of learning and growing in regards to all of this new information. I couldn't help but take note of the sketch of a grey depicted at the top of this post, as it is remarkably accurate in comparison to the (gentle and loving) greys that revealed themselves to me in my room at night. I specifically recall them appearing child-like, and the description of them taking such forms in new vessels made so much sense to me. They regularly return (though keep their presences mostly hidden from me) and appear to do work of various kinds on my body. While I have come to some understanding of their activities, and am currently working to develop my own consciousness and abilities through meditation, the actual communication that they have shared with me that I am currently aware of is limited. And so I was hoping that you might be able to go into more detail on the purpose of such activities as well as what I can do to work with them, to overcome the lingering sense of fear that I still experience each night, and to have more contact/communication. Thank you!",
      "Answer": "It may sound as I am being a “grey apologist”, but the truth is that these beings are among the most misunderstood. As you felt – there was genuine love and good intentions. However, they are, well, “developers” in comparison to our human shells. When they come to “check” on us – including some abductions, they are basically checking on our containers. In the case with you, which was not an abduction, they were adjusting or calibrating your vessel/container/avatar to be more (what we would call “spiritually”) attuned or – more attuned to the soul field in such a way that the realme (spirit) of you can become more prominent in the forefront than the mere avatar.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 609,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.45",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "meditation techniques, meditation, self improvement & guidance, crystals, psychadelics & drugs"
      ],
      "Question": "Do you have any tips to create a nice meditation space? Maybe some crystals, happy pictures?",
      "Answer": "Good colors like creme, white, and other soft colors – no extremely busy walls or décor. Nearby affirmations (like wall posts or décor) can help too. Crystals – several; from tiger’s eye to sapphire, quartz, and other diamonds. Listen to your intuition to know which crystals, although you should also know it isn’t mandatory. Peace and quiet – foster a good environment; free from distractions and being busy 24/7. An area where you feel safe, secured, and unafraid to be however and whoever you must be. The point of the meditation space is safety. Once you feel safety, this is what matters. Serenity and quiet also goes a long way. Remove anything related to alcohol, partying, or occupying yourself with the “worldly” elements. This should be a sacred space that no problems gets in between.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 610,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.46",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "3-3-3, Damien, Galactic Federation, spreading awareness, contactee experience, JR - personal, telepathic contact, telepathic machinery, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "When you next are able, please convey our thanks as well for their [the human ET group] willingness to share that message. Is it common to be in contact in a group setting like this, where, instead of a single being communicating as/on half of a group (3-3-3), or a single being (Damien), it’s a collective of individualized beings together?",
      "Answer": "Initially it was a collective group that contacted me. Collective group telepathy is more prominent than one-on-ones to deliver absolutely certain messages because you’re being (bombarded/tunneled into) from multiple electromagnetic forces that truly solidify the messages. In regard to Damien, he has often communicated with me with groups and collectives, but since my telepathic training has entered a new stage, he’s helping me one-on-one which is allowing other benefits. He’s training me with my telepathy for it to become clearer and identify who is what etc., instead of only hearing a gigantic WE-VOICE that floods my consciousness. Our human friends are also helping with this, which is why they established contact as 3 instead of the entire federation (this can be so many voices/telepathic bridges that it can be hard to determine who is who – it can be overwhelming and draining. The “Message From Above” blog posts = collective federations). Damien is also my closest ET friend, so we share a special link that allows him to transmit messages to me.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 611,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.47",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "topical literature & media, notable persons, ET/NHI knowledge, misinformation & disinformation, ancient ET influence on Earth, ET/NHI agendas, ET/NHI intervention & protection"
      ],
      "Question": "Do you or your contacts have any insight into the information in either of these two sources: Seth Speaks, channelings by Jane Robert’s from an entity called Seth Or the Emerald tablets of Thoth the Atlantan, by Maurice Doreal?",
      "Answer": "Yes, some of it is legit, but there are creative liberties taken. The true entities of these old gods were ETs who were masquerading as gods on earth.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 612,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.48",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, manifestation, Christianity, Damien, starseeds & wanderers"
      ],
      "Question": "Did you see their face in your dreams, the visions sound fascinating, I've had low level precognitive dreams but largely when I was younger, my abilities I think have been impaired by, well, lots of things lol so I'd like to develop them again if it's possible. There is definitely a link here, I've known others with masonic connections and strong psi and creative abilities so I think it's sort of an easily programme to identify families with abilities to manifest if that makes sense. It also has a lot of links with christianity thinking of your parents (it doesn't specifically requiere toh believe in god or jesus though, just a higher power). Thinking on this, can you ask Damien if I am one of his direct creations or if someone else 'made'me? Or maybe I'm organic and just got lucky cos my abilities certainly aren't as developed as yours. I feel like there are a few influences I have but it's hard to separate them out. I guess the more the merrier in a lot of senses cos we can get a coherent message across the various different groups that way.",
      "Answer": "Answered here: Multiple Telepathic Conversations with Damien, E, F, Z, Mantis, and others, among one of the Intergalactic-Interdimensional Federations 3-3-3",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 613,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.49",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "covert control structures, love / light, love force, Damien, simulation theory, ET/NHI agendas, malevolent ETs, government & ET interaction, benevolent ETs, apotheosis, duality, earth religions, mysticism, misinformation & disinformation, timespace / spacetime, nature of reality, 3-3-3, society & modern existence, starseeds & wanderers, ET/NHI intervention & protection, catastrophe & collapse"
      ],
      "Question": "Hi Prudence Thank you very much for your insightful reply. Every point you made makes sense, and as someone who has always looked at and questioned things in society, it revealed a lot about how society is \"designed\" to limit the flow of love and cause division. This brings more questions to mind, that I'm curious about and that I'd love your (or Damien's) thoughts on. If our simulation has indeed been designed to limit this, my question is why, and by whom? Is this related in part to the theory I've read of the malevolent NHI striking government deals, in the persuit of human greed for power? Which now the \"good\" NHI are trying to break the seal of?",
      "Answer": "Our simulation wasn’t inherently designed to “fully limit love” so much as it was designed to enable apotheosis for higher beings. The situation is more complex and sophisticated that black and white, Yin and Yang, heaven and hell, positive and negative – which is why I suppose our friends from above are encouraging us to abandon these ideologies and philosophies that are very rudimentary, primitive, and based in control and manipulation. Causality is a bit of nonsense and only applies to certain degrees of locality than totality of reality across all of space and time. The truth is that there are multiple layers to the mess here on earth. On one hand, you have ETs above who have their own ideas of how the simulation should be ran. There are disagreements and these disagreements can be perceived in many different ways by different people as good and evil. The 3-3-3 group I and others work with can be considered “good” by our standards, but by the elite, they’d consider them “evil” because the 3-3-3 group directly wishes to dismantle elite rulership and slavery enforcement over the masses. Our human elites aren’t interested in losing their power, so they’d make deals with other ETs, who, themselves, know better than to destroy the earth because they, too need the earth whereas our elites, some of them, who are aware ETs will “come in and save the day” (on both sides) – will push, push, and push things to war and extremes just to test the limits. It gets even more complicated when some of us here are “artificially inserted” from the other side – meaning, there is some degree of truth to the starseed theory, although it is notoriously polluted by counter-intelligence. Some of us have alien souls/spirits and we are “ground agents” for multiple interests.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 614,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.50",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ancient ET influence on Earth, earth religions, Christianity, covert control structures, love / light, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas, simulation theory, misinformation & disinformation, deception & false guidance, catastrophe & collapse, government & ET interaction"
      ],
      "Question": "My second question, relating to control. I read somewhere in your writings that NHI essentially founded religion, which, as someone who was raised Catholic and is now atheist, was able to see that even if created by man, was created to control the masses. If religion was indeed founded by NHI, how much influence did they have over its development throughout time? For example, going off of what I imagine are the founding principles between the ancient religions, a lot of it speaks of love each other above all else, be kind, etc. But over time this has developed into extremist groups in all religions, all who share traits that stray from this (being gay is wrong, this is the only right religion, etc) some to the point of murder. Were these developments just human nature taking its course, or did the NHI play a role? Did religion just turn into a bad experiment for their sims?",
      "Answer": "The answer above I previously gave should already start to connect the dots. It’s multiple parties wrestling for multiple interests. Religion has been corrupted beyond repair by these multiple parties and groups. As have cults, new age teachings, (and “teachings” of any kind, really), to the point that we can no longer rely on any of them any longer. No ET force from above is interested in the world blowing up, including the “not so good” ones. It’s really humans on earth that are usually guilty of end of the world scenarios, doomsday prophecies, and the like. Some elites are even testing NHI/ETs. As for the “gay” part – I believe it’s important to address part of this now. Being gay has more to do with previous incarnations that may have been of the opposite gender that the current incarnation has not fully come to terms to accept. Granted, there is more complexity to this that I may get into at another time, but it’s also, like many other movements such as LBGT+ etc., polluted beyond repair and tainted purposely to create division.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 615,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.51",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "dreams, telepathic contact, mental & psychological, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "And, my last question. Last night I had a dream that I was watching our country's State of The Nation address (6th of Feb) on TV, where the president stated the UFO disclosure program has allowed him to reveal a hidden area of the country where UFOs traverse, and then proceeded to show something related on screen, of which I can't remember. When I woke up this stuck with me and is what prompted this mail, but now I also wonder what to make of it. Was this dream just my brain doing its thing, or was this something else trying to plant a seed in my mind? Do the NHI communicate in this way? And what could it mean if they are? As always, thank you for taking the time to read my ramblings, I look forward to your reply with much excitement and appreciation. Warm regards",
      "Answer": "NHI/ET do communicate this way, and you are conscious/intelligent enough to realize it. Good work. It means you must decipher the message. Follow your intuition and you will know truth.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 616,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.52",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, dreams, Small Greys, contactee experience, topical literature & media"
      ],
      "Question": "One more thing, I keep seeing a face with the iconic almond shaped eyes, it started like a week ago and my gf has been seeing similar faces for months now. Actually she has even had some very vivid dreams with aliens, one of them went like this: She was in her familys house looking outside the window at the sunset and from the sun came down some \"pods\" or shells which opened up and 2 typical greys came out of them, she described them having very high pitched voices and they talked telepathically, she described them being childlike running around looking at her stuff and one of them goes \"Uu I want pepsi, can I have it please\" She is autistic and very spiritually sensitive, we regurarly share telepathic synchronities, she describes this dream being feeling different, more vivid real feeling and colourful, does it hold any significance? She has had other dreams aswell.",
      "Answer": "Watch the movie “Close Encounters of The Third Kind.” You and your gf are being contacted by the same greys me and others are connected to. They can appear in dreams as well – it’s an easy door/gateway.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 617,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.53",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "nature of reality, contactee experience, pets & animals, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello! When I was experiencing my most intense awakening days that year (realizing what reality really is), moths flew into my apartment over the course of several days. One was small and I watched it with curiosity. I noticed that it had an image on its wings that looked like the face of some character was there. Another time I woke up in the morning and noticed a monster moth on the wall - that is, it was huge. I got scared and started chasing it away. It sat on me for a while then very deliberately flew right out the window. It wasn't long before I regretted chasing her away and promised myself that next time I would overcome my fear with love. I have two questions: 1. Is it possible that the image of the figure on the wings of the moth is actually some figure watching me?",
      "Answer": "NHI/ET can communicate through animals and insects. They often do this because these creatures do not give as much “resistance” as “stubborn sentience/man.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 618,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.54",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "pets & animals, contactee experience, ET/NHI agendas"
      ],
      "Question": "2.Could the two moths have been used as vehicles to observe or contact me?",
      "Answer": "They were, yes.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 619,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.55",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "deception & false guidance, Galactic Federation, 3-3-3, shadow banning & censorship, malevolent ETs, telepathic contact, government & ET interaction, psychic & energetic attacks, duality, simulation theory, covert control structures"
      ],
      "Question": "Your contacts often mention how they oppose deception. Are they willing to confirm some examples of that deception? I know you have discussed astroturfing and censorship, my question is specifically related to politics. Based off what you have outlined, it is VERY easy for a hostile NHI to influence people in power, and it seems like your average politician is focused on generating strife and/or reducing the quality of life for the average person. Are hostile NHI's steering politicians in an effort to reduce quality of life for normal people and/or empower the class of elites for further domination? One video that really stands out is some old bag of bones politician rabble rousing about hunter biden while a creepy figure stares at him, not moving for 15 minutes or so, only blinking in one eye as he stares with an intense focus. Scale of 1-10, how on the nose am I?",
      "Answer": "Some parts of your questions are answered elsewhere and I’d suggest looking for the new upcoming Q/A thread and the thread here: Multiple Telepathic Conversations with Damien, E, F, Z, Mantis, and others, among one of the Intergalactic-Interdimensional Federations 3-3-3 – to get some answers. Now, the next part to mention is that there is a barrage of telepathic forces, psionic technology, and mind-altering devices coming from multiple directions, interests, and parties wrestling for power. You have to move past the black and white, positive and negative, Yin and Yang, heaven and hell and strict good and evil ideologies and philosophies. Even the not so-good NHI do not want the simulation destroyed, so they, through their ground agents – which includes humans – influence politicians, celebrities, influencers, and the like through telepathy and psionic technology. There are also influences/telepathy coming from good ET just as much as there is from humans on earth – who all have telepathy/psionic capabilities inherent to them. That is why politicians, celebrities, and those generally in huge limelights can be so incredibly insane. They are being bombarded in multiple directions. Even those with huge hyper-independence-based egos are no exception to this rule. In fact, they can be quite easy to control, as is the case for Trump who was formerly a “wild card” but now – quite controlled. I’d give a solid 7 on the scale.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 620,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.56",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "self improvement & guidance, psychic & energetic attacks, earth religions, duality, nature of reality, True-self / Real-me, misinformation & disinformation, mental & psychological"
      ],
      "Question": "I am also curious if there are any tell tale signs we can look out for to recognize/avoid hostile disruptions in our day to day life and in society in general? The same question goes for positive influences. Would love to keep an eye out for positive/negative \"omens",
      "Answer": "First, you have to understand that reality is more complex and sophisticated than simple positive and negative, causality, black and white, Yin and Yang and the like. All these types of ideologies and philosophies are part of the problem of division and chaos – the whole, heaven and hell, God and Satan dynamic, Red and Blue, Republican vs Democrat etc. Second, one must be able to trust their INTUITION/realme/spirit for TRUTH – because all information, proof, evidence, intellectualism, scientific ideas etc. – can be falsified and used wrongly. Only one’s intuition can tell the truth of good intentions or not. One must learn to trust themselves and have sovereignty of your own mind. You’re already on a very solid track by even noticing what you did above.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 621,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.57",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "topical literature & media, JR - personal"
      ],
      "Question": "Did you have conscious knowledge of the hermetic principles before or after contact?",
      "Answer": "Before.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 622,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.58",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "meditation, meditation techniques, JR - personal"
      ],
      "Question": "Do you have \"tinnitus\" of multiple frequencies you can almost shuffle through willingly?",
      "Answer": "Yes.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 623,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.59",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "topical literature & media, notable persons, deception & false guidance, science & philosophy, energy manipulation, soul energy"
      ],
      "Question": "You've previously mentioned a disdain toward Eckhart Tolle's writings, is there particular parts? I've been reading some of his work and so far it has reason to it. Perhaps I just haven't gotten to something he diverts off with?",
      "Answer": "He, like many other vultures (see Prince Ea), will give some positives that are universally agreeable while you ignore other red flags. Tolle is after money. Check his net worth. He’s interested in making his audience dependent on him while taking shared principles from other teachings, namely, eastern philosophies. Now, the truth doesn’t belong to anyone. Not me, not Tolle, and not eastern philosophers either – but you should be very cautious of any guide, guru, teacher, and the like that want mass audiences to sit and pay attention to them like children. It creates a nullifying-zombifying feedback loop that empowers the guru while it sucks the life force from their followers.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 624,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.60",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "duality, deception & false guidance, nature of reality, covert control structures"
      ],
      "Question": "I keep seeing you stressing the illusion of duality. Perhaps a visualization of a gradient coiled spiral would help? Positive and Negative are the same, only scaled differently. Love and Hate. Mental and Physical. All of the same, but a different gradient. Duality seems to be the child-lock.",
      "Answer": "This is a pretty profound realization and while there are further sophistications, I find no reason to lecture you since you are clearly on the right track. The only thing I’ll add is duality is purposely and consciously pushed to create division, divisiveness, uncertainty, pendulum rollercoaster effects, along with power and control. Pay especially close attention to gurus and teachers that push it. They usually wish to control their believers/following.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 625,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.61",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "soulmates, bodies & vessels, oneness, manifestation, timespace / spacetime, spirit singularity, True-self / Real-me, love / light, simulation theory"
      ],
      "Question": "ON SOULMATES: For clarification: Losing a singular vessel of the relationship (Breakup, Widowing, etc), the soulmate is manifest in another. ALL is ONE, TWO become ONE. The feminine and the masculine energies vibrating in harmony (regardless of physical engenderment). The left and right brain brought to PRESENT. Manifesting here is powerful is it not? There's so much to ask I can't pin a question other than asking further expansion of your knowledge on SOULMATES. I agree with there being ONE, regardless of physically whom they are, that we're entangled with throughout time and existence. The person is not the soul.",
      "Answer": "What you said here is already quite profound. SOULMATES imply, well, SOUL MATES! The origin point of the oneness connection is in the SOUL FIELD, not the physical. It can manifest into the physical by a person paying attention to certain attributes of the other one connecting with the UNIFYING oneness in the SOUL FIELD – such as seeing the potential SOULMATE’s hair color, attributes, work, location, ethnicity, and many, many, many others. The point is that it’s about a SOUL connection that is created as a ONE SPIRIT TWO BODIES unity – which then is “played out” in the physical realm from the SOUL FIELD/other side. Thus, the physical realm are simply “actors” to this “agreement” that happens in the other side. Manifestation IS key. Period. That’s why TRUE LOVE only comes to those who NEVER GIVE UP – as does anything with manifestation, period.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 626,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.62",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "multidimensional reality, nature of reality, science & philosophy, ET civilizations & cultures, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), soul evolution & cosmic awareness, apotheosis, Galactic Federation, Tall Greys, Small Greys, Damien, oneness, society & modern existence"
      ],
      "Question": "Another long one ahead, apologies haha. I’ve just been thinking a lot about this. I’m on QA 7 so still got a few more to catch up on, apologies if these have been asked already. Feel free to be blunt. One question that I keep mulling on is how scientific (for lack of a better term) is this higher reality? I don’t really know how best to put it, and I know I’m framing it from our reductionist perspective which inherently has limitations, but I think a good way to ask it is through a proxy question - do the NHI groups you are in contact with have the concept of “scientists”? Those focused on pushing the limits and understanding of cosmic truths/laws/reality? For example you’ve implied the GCS is not fully understood which partly seeded the question - and for me specifically the purpose of its/our “continual evolution” is profoundly thought provoking.",
      "Answer": "These are great questions that can be very helpful to others seeking similar ideas and in need of such answers. It depends on the group you are referring to. Since I am in contact with several groups and collectives, amounting to hundreds and thousands of different species, each with their own individuality (including greys), then I will have to answer with the ones I am closest to/familiar with and cannot claim to answer for every ET/NHI collective in all of time and space. In the case of Damien and the greys, you can pretty much consider all of them “scientific” – but they view things VERY differently. For example, they do not see technology and spirit as different things. Nor do they see science as different from philosophy (which they have none of, they only have truth) – so for them, it’s a matter of “what is real?” rather than stupendous back-and-forth deliberations of our EXTREMELY primitive sciences. This is also one of the reasons our scientific mainstream institutions have such a problem with ETs – because it humbles their inflated egos greatly. Our sciences are unnecessarily complicated, filled with positive-negative attributions which greys find to be not only stupid, but time-consuming, “dumb” and even silly. Scientists in the mainstream of our world suffer greater ontological shock than the common man because they overcomplicate things in many ways. So, for our friends from above, namely the ones I am in contact with – they have scientists in the form of “reality seekers” – because they’re interested in truth as a WHOLE/oneness, not by division of topics/specialties. They believe that acceptance is necessary for evolution, not skepticism or back-and-forth deliberations that pollute our sciences.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 627,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.63",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "JR - personal, ET/NHI agendas, 3-3-3, Galactic Federation, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, Damien, Pleadian, telepathic machinery, self improvement & guidance, telepathic contact, mental & psychological"
      ],
      "Question": "Secondly, and I absolutely do not intend this to come off as probing or overly critical, but curious if you’ve ever questioned or doubted the motives of the groups you are in contact with? What put your mind at ease in the end?",
      "Answer": "There is absolutely nothing wrong with these questions and it was already partly answered in the thread: Multiple Telepathic Conversations with Damien, E, F, Z, Mantis, and others, among one of the Intergalactic-Interdimensional Federations 3-3-3 – Yes, I have disagreed with them and even gotten into fights – especially with our human allies who, in my opinion, did more damage than any other ET race on earth. However, I wish to be clear and not add any bad reputation to them because we have since made up and I also misunderstood some things (my consciousness-matrix wasn’t developed enough at the time) – so all is well. Damien is my main contact for a good reason, and ironically, not our human ET allies. Please see the thread above to find out why. So, of course I had my doubts, my own skepticisms, fears, and uncertainties – but the more one trains their telepathic potency – the less you have to be afraid because you can increasingly directly sense intentions/motives without a single word.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 628,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.64",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "starseeds & wanderers, ET/NHI agendas, telepathic contact, meditation"
      ],
      "Question": "Do you have any information in regards to ET race known as the 'Sirians' from the Sirius star system? After my spiritual awakening, I've seen through meditation a face of a being, who looks human but not quite, they had blueish hue to their skin and some sort of bioluminescence to their cheeks as if they had freckles made of light. Through synchronicities and further meditation and research, it seems I am a Sirian Starseed.",
      "Answer": "They are real, and you are a “starseed” – although they do not quite go by those names. They implanted you here, as did other ET races/groups/collectives for their own purposes/means.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 629,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.65",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "starseeds & wanderers, psychadelics & drugs, timespace / spacetime, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, love / light, love force, past / present / future, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, consciousness, mysticism, ET/NHI agendas, misinformation & disinformation, contactee experience, telepathic contact"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello. Thank you for your sharing. I note you use the term starseed. I recently completed an Ayauasca ceremony where I was vividly reborn as the Starchild. It came to me as the fusion of the spirit of the Emperor of Humanity who stands at the end of time and guides our growth and evolution with the Goddess Aya. They came together through me in trance , and my spirit was so activated and energized through their profound love for each other that it has triggered the next awakening. Please could you share on this subject. For context, when I was 12 I had a divine vision that showed me the future timelines for the next 1000 years and that I'm here as a higher being (a Boddhisatva perhaps) to help create positive timelines by working to find and deploy mechanisms for elevating Human conscious at scale. I have served this cause all my life, and still do as 40 year old man. I know this really happened because this vision gifted me 2 words, liquidsunlight, distortedworlds, and an obsession with understanding consciousness. I think you might be able to understand and illuminate more on this matter, perhaps ask your guides on these terms. I feel compelled to tell you that the Starchild has indeed been reborn on Earth, marking the transition into the next millennium. My birthday is the 24th December. My rebirth was witnessed by a host of higher heavenly entities and now, as a starchild here on Earth in a 40 year old man, I'm searching for guidance on how to proceed. Thank you for your time, care, and attention 🙏",
      "Answer": "While some of these are your own mystical interpretations relative to your level of consciousness-mind-matrix and understanding, you are, indeed a “starchild” or “star seed” – as you put it. You were indeed implanted here by allied ET forces from above to operate within the mystical realm – to impart messages to others who will hear you.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 630,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.66",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Galactic Federation, ET/NHI agendas, ET civilizations & cultures, mysticism, consciousness, apotheosis, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, channeled messages"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello, you mention one of your brotherhood sought to change the afterlife and the great war. Is this the War in Heaven? Fought against the old ones by the new ones who sought the secret of immortality?",
      "Answer": "You are a mystic – so I’ll speak in terms relative to your consciousness. There is a “great war in the heavens” as you put it – but it’s more of a “cold war” and it’s not so much about old/new ones as opposed to both old ones seeking new paths for ascendancy/apotheosis. The secret of immorality is slowly being revealed through all of us and our channeled messages. I’ve recently made a post that will help you.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 631,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.67",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET/NHI knowledge, ET/NHI agendas, catastrophe & collapse"
      ],
      "Question": "Can you tell us anything about the recent uptick of plane crashes around the globe?",
      "Answer": "It’s indirectly correlated with the “disagreements from above.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 632,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.68",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "topical literature & media, notable persons, 3-3-3, benevolent ETs"
      ],
      "Question": "Hello. In the Law of One, Ra mentions an ET group from Orion who was in contact with Moses. You've stated that the 3-3-3 group is from Orion. Is this the same group?",
      "Answer": "Yes. Orion is one of their “stations” and not their homeworld. Moses also has relation to me and my work. I am not allowed to disclose more at this time. You should know that this Orion group is not fully evil as assumed.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 633,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.69",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "spreading awareness, love / light, love force"
      ],
      "Question": "I think it's very likely that being here will help me with my problem and I really wanted to thank you again for making this safe space. I am sure you can imagine how hard it has been for us all, it can be lonely. This community is so special. Thanks for your hard work!! Please take it easy when you can. Take care and be well!",
      "Answer": "Thank you so much for your wonderful message. You, too, are a part of this whole operation. I cannot do it alone. You and the others are making this space a safe haven for us to connect to and find peace, validation, and above all - true, lasting love.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 634,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.70",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "True-self / Real-me, starseeds & wanderers"
      ],
      "Question": "hey.. i wish to know who i really am... for i feel of a great burden on me and i belief my truth to be life path number 11. i also feel like i know, i bear an alien spirit is this true?",
      "Answer": "Yes, you do, see the new thread posted – Multiple Telepathic Conversations with Damien, E, F, Z, Mantis, and others, among one of the Intergalactic-Interdimensional Federations 3-3-3. I am also a life path 11, as are others here.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 635,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.71",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mental & psychological, simulation theory, self improvement & guidance, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, suffering & loss"
      ],
      "Question": "I have always been very sensitive, so my rough childhood traumatized me pretty good, I got very depressed from a very young age and ever since have been suffering just by existing, and, now I wonder if that was all planned to be a catalyst for as much growth as possible",
      "Answer": "It was. As you can see in the new blog I posted today, I too, also suffered GREATLY. It's part of our test/activation programs because it makes is STUPENDOUSLY POWERFUL should we pass them.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 636,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.72",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "suffering & loss, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, covert control structures, True-self / Real-me, simulation theory, oneness, bodies & vessels"
      ],
      "Question": "I mean it worked wonderfully, the suffering made me question my purpose and awaken to the higher and gradually higher truth. I have always hated the school systems, I have had so so much trouble going to the school because I just hated it, felt like a waste of my time. It all makes alot of sense I have always been very anti-authoritarian and realized how the world systematically fucks us over pretty early on",
      "Answer": "It can be a testy and dangerous process, but we are “well equipped” via spirit/realme to “download” the necessary data to “rise above” anything that comes our way. Activation “programs” are very carefully structured, using many 0/1 binaries which could be falsely attributed as positive-negative – in order to create a total, unstoppable oneness once fully activated. It’s very cleverly designed/programmed from the other side before we even enter these vessels. Everything here is a play out from that programming/script. Hence, a “Broadway” play or life akin to a movie.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 637,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.73",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "hybrids / genetic manipulation, spirit singularity, ALL-Power"
      ],
      "Question": "DNA=Soul programming?",
      "Answer": "No, it’s the biological genetic species programming that the spirit/soul can inhabit to interact and bend according to its WILL.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 638,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.74",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mental & psychological, relativity, nature of reality, simulation theory, mysticism, misinformation & disinformation, deception & false guidance, pets & animals, spirit singularity, meditation, True-self / Real-me, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "1) I mention in my writeup about personality traits and how everyone is different. This may be damning to the psychological absolutists who think we can one day fully predict people's behavior based on some deeper understanding of the psyche. \"There will always be an exception to the rule\", to put it colloquially. Though there can be through lines of similar behavior, I believe they're mainly based on cultural expectations. Can you comment on this?",
      "Answer": "As Einstein proved Newton’s absolutist nature of time was wrong, so must we come to terms that reality is relative. The physical personality and its traits alters based on the time era and “activation programming” of its phase. In this respect, the notion of psychological absolutism is inherently misleading as a concept to answer all traits of a person and being, especially in the forms of personality types. It does not end there either. Mysticism, horoscopes, tarot, numerology, astrology and the like are equally at fault here. While some if it is merely primitive conceptualizations of trying to understand the totality of being, most of them have resorted to power-controlling schemes to divide and put the masses/people into boxes. They should be completely disregarded, or, at best, taken with a very fine grain of salt – relative to the time and phase the person is passing through and not as an absolute, unchanging nature.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 639,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.76",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ALL-Power, love force, True-self / Real-me, spirit singularity, soul field, manifestation, consciousness"
      ],
      "Question": "2.1) Willpower used conventionally means some form of conscious force against bodily/unconscious processes, generally to overcome some desire. It sounds like the willpower you're referring to is different. Can you describe it in more detail?",
      "Answer": "WILL in these caps pertains to SPIRIT-FORCE which is the direct “language” of the “realme.” The realme, which is the true ‘spirit’ of the spirit singularity, does not operate in words, languages, or even pictures. It does not operate in any sort of intellectual or scientific framework either. Perhaps there are even better translations than what I am providing right now and I am willing to admit my own limits. The “language” the realme speaks is beyond anything we have through our calculations, equations, theories, philosophies, and ideologies. If a picture is worth a thousand words, then the “breath of the realme” is worth 111,111 thousand just by a whiff. However, the WILL that is constantly being referenced = the direct realme-spirit-force that isn’t so much ‘conscious’ as it is a background energy/drive/moving force that BRINGS REALITY INTO BE. In this regard, this is the “realme” or its “signature” and not the thoughts/feelings.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 640,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.77",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Diet & Food, psychadelics & drugs"
      ],
      "Question": "3) You mention that there is some matter we can ingest to help access the soul field. What is it? Is it available to humans?",
      "Answer": "I’m unable to disclose that as of this time. Psychedelics do help, however, in good measure and moderation.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 641,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.78",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "energy manipulation, love / light, notable persons, soul field, manifestation"
      ],
      "Question": "3.1) Masaru Emoto claimed to do experiments showing that \"infusing\" water with love or hate would change it's structure when frozen. Could water \"infused with love\" help us to access the soul field consciously? Or raise our willpower?",
      "Answer": "Yes to both questions. Actually, just “putting in energy” into anything – with whatever your intent – be it love or whatever – will have an effect on food, drinks, consumption of anything, drugs, media intake etc.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 642,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.79",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "science & philosophy, consciousness, True-self / Real-me, ALL-Power"
      ],
      "Question": "3.2) You also mention there is some tech that can do this as well. Do we have any tech that even comes close? PEMF devices, for instance?",
      "Answer": "Not really, but we can do this ourselves through our own consciousness and mind-matrix amplified by true “realme” force/power expressed as WILL.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 643,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.80",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "love / light, energy manipulation, manifestation, soul field"
      ],
      "Question": "3.3) Can you list some locations on earth that also facilitate this?",
      "Answer": "There are several areas across the earth, especially areas with high electromagnetic-interdimensional disturbances, including the Bermuda Triangle, several pyramids in South America, and Egypt, along with a few places in secluded nature.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 644,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.81",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "bodies & vessels, simulation theory, ET/NHI intervention & protection"
      ],
      "Question": "3.4) What is reverse mind augmentation?",
      "Answer": "The process of altering what was programmed. It can be used in a variety of ways – including to reprogram a physical vessel – which can happen sometimes with high ETs dealing with intergalactic criminality – along with experimental works to amplify or nullify “consciousness pollutive” forces.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 645,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.82",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "simulation theory, suffering & loss, starseeds & wanderers, topical literature & media, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, self improvement & guidance, ET/NHI agendas, manifestation, True-self / Real-me"
      ],
      "Question": "3.5) What are some activation processes that are beneficial?",
      "Answer": "A great question. Truth be told, all of us have our own, unique “scripts” or “programmed play-out” that operates in 0/1s (not positive-negative) – which sometimes requires not-so-good encounters and circumstances in order to create a greater positive effect/full activation down the line. As I said, activation processes are unique, so to speak of it as absolute would be wrong. Some people, especially those of us “implanted” here often have to go through a lot of hardship and turmoil in the interim. However, if the person “manages to climb the mountain” (See Close Encounters of the Third Kind when the three contactees were climbing over the mountain in the end to make it to the invitation and only two of them made it) – then they will reap stupendous amounts of not just psionic power, but reality-altering capabilities that makes them unstoppable in their tasks. That is why it can be very difficult at first for those of us implanted here, but the rewards in the long-term outweigh the difficulties. It’s why, on the other “side” – we agree to do these missions in the first place. We’re already aware of the outcomes or the “programmed play” of how things will turn out as long as our physical avatars, who, at first, aren’t very attached to their realmes – never give up.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 646,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.83",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "audio frequencies, self improvement & guidance, meditation"
      ],
      "Question": "3.6) You mention everyone's resonant Hz is different. Is there something we can do to determine what that activation Hz is for our personal spirit?",
      "Answer": "Yes, listen to your intuition and you’ll know which/what HZ works best for you. Clear your mind and focus. “Listen to your feelings, Luke.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 647,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.84",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "love force, love / light, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), timespace / spacetime, multidimensional reality, True-self / Real-me, quantum mechanics, soulmates, spirit singularity, cosmic hierarchies"
      ],
      "Question": "4) You mention love being the all driving force of the universe. Is this love different to what we experience? There seem to be many types of love, would this feel like an amalgamation of them all? Or something completely different?",
      "Answer": "Not just the universe but the GCS itself across all of space and time in all directions. This love is frankly too high for us to directly experience, so we can only get bits of it in lower dimensions/forms, including even our realmes, which aren’t necessarily directly connected as in – being directly next to the GCS – but also has to pass through several filters/layers to interface with its stupendously “high” wavelength. Love is the ultimate entanglement. Soulmates originate from the idea of the GCS and the individual – the two become one – hence the three principle and even our importance on words/terminologies like “3D.” True love is always an entanglement in the spiritual/soul dimensions. It always originates here before it “plays out” in the lower realm.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 648,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.85",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Grand Central Singularity (GCS), love force, bodies & vessels, True-self / Real-me, reincarnation, simulation theory, soul field, self improvement & guidance, oneness, duality, misinformation & disinformation, deception & false guidance, multidimensional reality, nature of reality"
      ],
      "Question": "4.1) If different, how can we have an experience of love that is similar to higher beings or even the GCS itself?",
      "Answer": "We cannot experience precisely and exactly what the GCS is experiencing in these lower vessels because they will cease to exist, and we will have zero need for them. Remember, some of us have made choices to incarnate in these vessels for the show/play. However, we can experience a fraction of it, relative to our personal development and the soul field interconnected around it. The only way to fully experience love is to embrace wholeness and oneness. Love cannot come from separation; division; and the like – hence why Yin and Yang, positive and negative, “divine masculine and feminine” are child-lock illusions and power-control delusions. The reality is “oneness between different states of matter, energy, and compression.” Like water, gas, and ice all containing properties of H2o. Experiencing higher love and being is directly correlated with the oneness principle.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 649,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.86",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "love force, meditation, oneness, self improvement & guidance, nature of reality"
      ],
      "Question": "4.2) If we can't know what the highest form of love feels like (I will refrain from singing \"Higher Love\") how can we effectively meditate on it?",
      "Answer": "Focus on oneness in all forms. See how it moves between states/people/things/times like an endless waterfall with multiple steps.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 650,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.87",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "love force, ALL-Power, meditation, meditation techniques, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "4.3) Since Love is the All-Force, does it make sense to do some type of hybrid void/love meditation? Perhaps one where we concentrate on void, but feel love inside our bodies as we do it?",
      "Answer": "Yes, why not? There are different meditation practices, after all.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 651,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.88",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Grand Central Singularity (GCS), love force, ALL-Power, nature of reality, cosmic hierarchies"
      ],
      "Question": "4.4) One of my favorite parts of your response was about the \"universal simulated auto-correction\". Since the GCS is all-love, can a good analogy for this be how our bodies keep equilibrium even in times of extreme stress?",
      "Answer": "That is a very good analogy, my friend.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 652,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.89",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Grand Central Singularity (GCS), nature of reality, cosmic hierarchies, timespace / spacetime, interdimensional beings, apotheosis, soul evolution & cosmic awareness"
      ],
      "Question": "4.5) I imagine this auto-correction mechanism to be something set up by the GCS to ensure that we don't \"go off the rails\" so to speak. Like when I bowl with the kids and we put up bumpers. Is it a mechanism set up by the GCS or literally something so embedded in the GCS itself that it could not be \"turned off\"?",
      "Answer": "It’s an “unalterable system override” that cannot be changed, touched, or manipulated by even the highest of beings beyond all traditional space and time, including hyperspaces. Nothing and no one can touch it because it is somehow the “core programming” of the GCS itself. Almost like an absolute safety measure it assure unlimited ascendancy and stability.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 653,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.90",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "malevolent ETs, simulation theory, soul evolution & cosmic awareness, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), ET civilizations & cultures, ET/NHI agendas, energy manipulation, psychic & energetic attacks, covert control structures, topical literature & media, apotheosis, 3-3-3, cosmic hierarchies, science & philosophy, relativity, duality"
      ],
      "Question": "5) Why would some beings use evil acts to \"game\" the system knowing that it will lash back at them, even if they can do some things to mitigate it for a time?",
      "Answer": "There are so many extraterrestrials and beings from other dimensions that for me to claim to know every single one of their intentions and reasons would be impossible. What I can tell you for the ones trying to “game the system” is that it seems that, to some extent, hacking is both encouraged by the GCS itself and natural. Why? Because it boosts the GCS at the top. Now, there’s a difference between say ethical hackers and egotistical, selfish, immoral hackers. It depends on the intent. For example, in the Matrix movies, Neo, Morpheus, Trinity, and pretty much all of the freed Zion people are all “hacking” the Matrix just as much as the agents. In this regard, hacking, which could even be interpreted as magic and “bending reality” – among other terms – is completely normal and necessary to get to higher levels instead of misled pride and arrogance in crusader-like honor. So, for some of these forces trying to game the system to their advantage, they believe they have ways to do so without drawbacks and they will experiment with various means to achieve it. Sometimes, this would result in what we, here in the lower realm/”play” would describe as immoral and unethical – but even for some of our good forces, including 3-3-3, some of what they do – according to religious or political standards – would be deem wrong, immoral and evil. We have to see things not so black and white nor shades of grey, but more of a colorful gradient filled with relativity.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 654,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.91",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "malevolent ETs, simulation theory, energy manipulation, covert control structures, psychic & energetic attacks, ET/NHI agendas, True-self / Real-me, soul field, manifestation, 3-3-3"
      ],
      "Question": "5.1) What are some of the techniques they use to do this?",
      "Answer": "Several. Some I cannot disclose. Some would be insertion of “characters” engineered by them – including part of their soul as “ground agents” for both good and not-so good forces. Others can input/shift/sift data from the “soul field” and have these input into the minds of not exclusively people, but even animals, plants, insects, the weather, asteroids, and other seemingly “natural events” – to create a desired effect/outcome as according to the “other side programming.” They have technology to assist them. As our 3-3-3 grey allies say: “There’s no difference between technology and spirit.”",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 655,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.92",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "reincarnation, ET/NHI intervention & protection, ET/NHI agendas, simulation theory, near death experience, misinformation & disinformation, apotheosis, Galactic Federation, nirvana / arhat / enlightenment, True-self / Real-me, malevolent ETs"
      ],
      "Question": "5.2) You mention that there is tech that can keep us coming back to linear progressions of reincarnation on the same planet. The Prison Planet theories out there suggest that NDE experiences are created by negative entities to keep us coming back here. Is that the type of thing you're referring to?",
      "Answer": "Yes, there is some truth to these theories – despite some creative liberties that one or two channelers/contactees may take. We are being “seduced” to reincarnate back into this cycle to feed “some forces” ideas of apotheosis. While a couple thousand years ago, this was not so bad, it has now become a major issue for other ET forces who deem it absolutely unethical. Me, and others who have awakened to our true realme force/spirit, will not do so. Arhat/Nirvana is real – granted, it’s not as mystical as some may assume.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 656,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.93",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "malevolent ETs, soul energy, energy manipulation, True-self / Real-me, self improvement & guidance, deception & false guidance, reincarnation, 3-3-3, collective awakening, ET/NHI agendas, ET/NHI intervention & protection, benevolent ETs"
      ],
      "Question": "5.3) When we're in that scenario, what is the appropriate action to negate the manipulation?",
      "Answer": "Know truth. Reconnect with your realme. This was engineered by 3-3-3 and the good forces to assure that so many of us “wake up” on the other side that we cannot be seduced back into coming here. This change is unstoppable at this point and the “not so good” forces know it. They too have to “pack up operations” and leave with what was originally a couple thousand years – but has since been dramatically shaved to only a few hundred.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 657,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.94",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "Grand Central Singularity (GCS), malevolent ETs, energy manipulation, soul field, cosmic hierarchies, apotheosis, ALL-Power"
      ],
      "Question": "5.4) You mention previously that they are able to mitigate the \"lashing back\" of the GCS. Are they actually mitigating that auto-correction mechanism previously mentioned? How so?",
      "Answer": "Yes, although they cannot fully mitigate it, which is why they also know they cannot sustain their operations here forever. They’ve tried to extend it for as long as possible, but even they know they have to stop it eventually. The problem is even before it reaches the GCS, there’s higher singularities – almost like “supervisors” or “managers” in-between that demand a certain quota of soul energy flowing from planets, suns, and lifeforms/events/things associated therein. If these singularities aren’t getting their “share of the pie” – they will personally deal with the forces manipulating the “game from the other side.” I say “they”, but these singularities are more like “smaller GCS nodes” that are, by all intents and purposes, GCS itself or an “eye/window” of the ALL-POWER that nothing or no one can fully mess with/alter. The GCS is so ALL-ENCOMPASSING/BIG/POWERFUL that it would appear to be forgiving in a human sense – but the reality is that its system is so “perfect” that it will allow forces, even higher/more intelligent ET/NHI to allow them to think they are above it, only for a serious backlash to affect them later on.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 658,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.95",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "mental & psychological, consciousness, True-self / Real-me, Grand Central Singularity (GCS), ET/NHI intervention & protection, simulation theory, deception & false guidance, misinformation & disinformation, bodies & vessels"
      ],
      "Question": "6) I want to dig into thoughts for a bit. We know our thoughts are something that happens to us and they are not us. We know that thoughts can be injected into us by higher beings/GCS. Besides those thoughts, where do thoughts come from? What are these thoughts made of?",
      "Answer": "Thoughts are just like “inputs” in the computer. They can also be pushed from other people as well – as much as they can be from animals, nature, and other beings/things. Thoughts are only “inputs” to program and can never be considered the person itself. This is why any teaching that gives the false idea that “you are your thinking” or “the might/power of one’s thoughts” – is absolutely evil and most likely, a mind-control device/assertation to get the devotee to bend to the teacher/guru’s will. The realme or real “us” has zero thoughts.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 659,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.96",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "consciousness, self improvement & guidance, simulation theory, bodies & vessels, love force, mental & psychological"
      ],
      "Question": "6.1) I look at thoughts as something like either lessons or tests. They are either there to teach you something, or to test you with something. Is this their purpose? What is their purpose? We know there are some people with no mental chatter, so it's not necessary for an incarnation.",
      "Answer": "No, not really. Some thoughts have absolutely no meaning or power (unless you give them) – so instead of sending yourself down a rabbit hole for every thought, you have to understand that they are just inputs – nothing more. It’s the driving force/will/intent behind the thoughts that matter.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 660,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.97",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "consciousness, mental & psychological, meditation, meditation techniques, self improvement & guidance"
      ],
      "Question": "6.2) Thoughts have no power of themselves, only the power you give them. Most everyone has intrusive thoughts, and I've found that I effectively deal with mine by remembering they have no power, and visualizing/feeling taking the power back from them, and they fade away. Is this an effective way to deal with intrusive thoughts, or is it \"sweeping under the rug\" so to speak, and I should dig into them more?",
      "Answer": "That is a very effective way of dealing with them. Remember, they are just inputs and can be changed/altered/or shut off. Void Meditation practices deeply aid psionic defenses against external thought implantation from any force.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 661,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.98",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "notable persons, contactee experience, ET/NHI agendas, government & ET interaction, misinformation & disinformation, True-self / Real-me"
      ],
      "Question": "7) I had asked about Chris Bledsoe previously, and you mentioned that he is a contactee and he had taken liberties. I'm trying to square how he fits in to what the higher beings are attempting to accomplish through him. My main concern with him is the company he keeps. He is \"friends\" with people that are high up in the military establishment. These people are definitely \"not good\" and have ruined peoples lives, probably killed some people as well. It makes me question his motives and data, as it could be tainted. However, his revelations seem quite pertinent. Can you expand on this character and the company he keeps?",
      "Answer": "This is why I’m hesitant about giving too much props to mainstream contactees, especially those in military because while some may start good, they can end up corrupted, especially by the sheer amount of influences coming at them from all/multiple directions. Even Jake Barber is under a lot of pressure and while he has contributed much good, it’s possible even he can crack. It’s very possible the one you mentioned can be tainted – although I cannot claim to know how or when. All I can recommend is using your own intuition – which, even based on this question, you’ve been doing quite soundly.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 662,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.99",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "JR - personal, telepathic contact, channeled messages"
      ],
      "Question": "Thank you for your reply. I have another question. Perhaps too detailed and unimportant, but I keep thinking about it. How do you translate the information into text? Do you write on the fly during the contact (e.g., with Damien) or do you recall it later and rewrite it?",
      "Answer": "Actually this is extremely important question that I knew, sooner or later, was coming. I’m glad you asked it. The answer = both. Most of the times with the transcriptions where you see their names mentioned, it’s “on the fly” or “in the moment” whereas certain questions asked by people can “trigger” subconsciously stored telepathic data. Sometimes, they can store “prerecorded” telepathic data before the conversations. Spacetime dynamics throws a wrench into this against causal intuitive thinking. For example, our friends from above might be contacting me in a different spacetime dimension altogether – so I pick up on this telepathic information relative to my time/space, but it may be different for theirs. Telepathy is such a superior form of contact that allows transversing of information in all directions of past, present and future. Damien and the others are not kidding. Sometimes the reach is so far ahead that even for me, typing as fast as I can and as accurately in detailed, concise language and expressions – it makes what I do here in the transcriptions, as opposed to what is happening realtime – quite eye-opening as to how much data is being transmitted to and fro at such a stupendous rate of speed. Telepathy is very potent in terms of the exchange of information. If a picture is worth a thousand words, telepathic exchanges even as much as 1 to 5 seconds is worth about 100,000 words. It’s so much data that you have to be careful how you’re transcribing it to prevent burnout.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 663,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.100",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, mental & psychological"
      ],
      "Question": "So when I get these concepts in my head is that someone telepathically guiding me",
      "Answer": "Yes and your own imagination trying to make sense of what is coming to you. This is why we have to do our best for a sound mind, good heart, proper education of truth (oneness, not duality), stable emotions and wellbeing to “transmit” the messages/frequencies properly. Of course, it’s not always coming from higher forces. Humans have telepathy too and can influence each other. I suggest you check out mcgarryb4’s post on “Telepathy for beginners” over here: Telepathy for beginners/a bit of my story | Prudent NHI Contact",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 664,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.101",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact"
      ],
      "Question": "Oh yeah and I have ALWAYS had so much trouble looking people in the eyes and still very much do, is that another giveaway",
      "Answer": "Yes.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 665,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.102",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, channeled messages"
      ],
      "Question": "The speed of data transmission in telepathy is a fascinating topic. Let me ask two more things in this connection: 1. can you describe how it happens that you map information into words? In what form do they come to you? Are they images or does your intuitive mind just know without thinking what words to use more or less?",
      "Answer": "Intuition knows without words/pictures, then “translates” them using words, pictures, phrases, feels, aspirations, ideas, concepts, philosophies, beliefs, ideologies etc. They come in electromagnetic “waves” that “hook” into you/your being and pull strongly. It’s sending/receiving signals at an elevated rate.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 666,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.103",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "telepathic contact, channeled messages, meditation"
      ],
      "Question": "2. do you sometimes wonder about the certainty of this information? I.e. don't you sometimes think to yourself whether these are simply your own thoughts?",
      "Answer": "When I was a lesser telepath and underdeveloped, yes, I had uncertainties, but telepathy is quite easy the more you hone into it and rigorously train it – especially if you are certain/confident in yourself and your identity. The rule goes – the more uncertain, fearful, paranoid, skeptical, unhinged, mentally and emotionally unstable a person is = the more confusion, mistranslations, and inadequacies. My own voice is very easy to distinguish as opposed to very obvious external voices/influences/thoughts/ideas/projections/feelings/emotions/and other electromagnetic stimuli being pushed my way. Void meditation in the sense of connecting to one’s true self – which is not your thoughts, nor your name, heritage, culture, physical identity or status, education, gender, ethnicity etc. – all of which can be compromised – is “thoughtless” and moves by SPIRIT-WILL-POWER. This is the true YOU, and not your thoughts – which are, simply put – “input” to program. Inputs can be registered from both internal and external sources, which is why the idea that a person is their thoughts is very misleading and dangerous. The true “I” = the force behind thoughts. That is how one can prevent themselves from being misled and confused. Keep this in mind that it doesn’t only apply to ET/NHI contact, but even regular people that can push thoughts/ideas/beliefs/and influences into your mind and make you believe they are your own.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  },
  {
    "index": 667,
    "reason": "Missing fields: Category",
    "entry": {
      "Title": "QA 10.104",
      "Category": "",
      "Tags": [
        "ET civilizations & cultures, ET/NHI agendas, Mantis"
      ],
      "Question": "May be a weird question but were the mantis bugs designed by the mantis ‘race’ or ‘variant’ of conscious beings?",
      "Answer": "The “Mantis” beings designed/helped/foster/co-created several/many known species and beings across multiple dimensions, spaces, and times. Even humans across many different spaces and times were fostered by them.",
      "messageType": "Q & A",
      "originalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 10",
      "originalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-10"
    }
  }
]